bakerella.com 2019-07-19

# Privacy Policy – bakerella.com

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Bakerella.com. By using the Bakerella website, you are consenting to the practices described in this privacy policy, which may also be modified from time to time by us and updated on this page.

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us by way of commenting, email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. 

**Information we collect**  
We collect information when you register to receive emails from us, when you contact us or when you comment on Bakerella.com. That information includes username and email address. However, you may also choose to comment anonymously. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an prize. 

**Log files**  
Like many websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. 

**Cookies**  
We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site. Some of our advertisers may use cookies on our site. However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Sharing**  
We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

**Third Party Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Surveys and Giveaways**  
From time-to-time our site requests information via surveys or giveaways. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

**Contact**  
If you have questions about this privacy policy, related to the site, you should contact us at bakerella at earthlink dot net.

Updated August 11, 2011
